ok let's play you can start here
and go first one everyone strong clap
semi final first match make some noise
great liling and what sound first
ball in to the block hole to start
so semi final one started n Diesels
vs Pink Panthers Pink Panthers
elect to field
first eight over
match semi final one Rahul Panchal and Mitesh
Chauhan the opening pair have bowled
each
step two balls ball two for no
loss single run
heard Mitesh Chauhan
strike become wide up
after three balls fo f no ls n Dazzlers
swing miss b just eyed out line white
sill umpire fo b bo f
ic laddbrokes premier league 205 are
now entered into the semi final round
first semi final in progress n Diesels vs
Pink Panthers
four balls six runs
no wicket first wicket
first wicket fall of n
Diesel five balls six runs one wicket take
good catch taken by
Vikas Vikas has made the team's Vikas
five balls six runs one wicket
five balls bowled six five balls bowled six five  Dazzlers
a new batsman Siddhesh More the all-rounder
from N Dazzlers
fielder there at wash
long single run
so single to end of the over good start
from Pink Panthers one was gun to for ao
N Dazzlers
so very good start from Hemant Ambekar
back to back three dots into the block
hole N Dazzlers
1.37 fw N
Dazzler kang sh ve
sir tremendous
sixer across for six runs straight
into the constellation one the ch on N
Dazzlers Siddhesh More strike well well
long on for
six looking to play over covers gets
outside edge only single
run ICC Labad Brokers Premier League 205
Day Two Season Two very
good shot alti palti de ghum ke jio
player wahe wahe cha run for four runs
this is the end of the over after two overs
on 18 N
Dazzlers Season Two Day Two End Even Sporting
Partner Brand Nex Media
TVS Match Semi-Final One in Progress
2.1
1941 Now  Parshuram the new
ball Para
Shram Parshuram
Para
Shram bowling left round wicket
str
feed two the two b par one N Diesels semi-final
one who will win and go enter the finals
which team will enter the finals four big contenders in the semi-finals
what
2.3 21 Fav N
Diesels something different something
special Mitesh
Yohan 2.4 2241 N
Diesels so very good feed there
so single to end of the
over Gun 25 N
XL Mitesh Chan bang with no four and Siddhesh
More 13 of 10 with one maximum
hit three overs 25 par one
[music]
it's very well played Ts Gun bowler fielder
running but ball win the race cracking
boundary what signal by
umpire 3 dti 32 par one N Diesels
3.3 32
Fav this time played and the ball goes
outside the boundary for four runs back
to back
boundaries at boundaries from Mitesh  Chauhan
to swing n miss good bowling from Vikash
Shukla
late four overs game over for 37 one N
Dazzlers
semi-final one in
progress ICC Lord Bucks Premier
League
2025 Day Two Now We entered in the semi-final
game
B
bowling
var per
kadam per kadam bearing ale hai Pratik Kadam one
over one seven runs one
wicket 4.18 N
Dazzlers Siddhesh
More oh but he is well inside the
crease very good running quick running
quick running by Mitesh Chauhan
4.2 39 fw N
Dazzlers very good bowling will they come back for
two bit of miss field
4.3
41 N Dazzlers
coming back for two more
two runs taken by Siddhesh More
Siddhesh More Mitesh
Chauhan four p
44 N Dazzlers initially pink path toss
elected to bowl first and they allay a low two but
first very good shot excellent timing
reverse shot for run ali palti de ghuma ke
four runs
4 the p 48 fw Mitesh Chauhan is doing amazing
25 12 balls four fours
4.5 48 for one last ball of the fifth
over very good and follow through by Pratik
Kadam
late bowl two overs 177 for one after four 49
F V A Diesels
after five overs 9 F V A
Diesels five overs 49 for one five-for 49 one
wicket down
score very big shot played in the gap
no fielder
or covers there the in field for four runs
and with this four runs 50 runs completed A D
Diesels 5.1 531
Mitesh Chauhan doing something special in this
match 30 14 with four
fours cracking shot no
fielder or the fielder this time to stop the
mid wicket region for a couple of runs
taken 32 with four fours 55 V A
Diesels we can pretty much now the score is 8
plus to clear the infield and will go all the way out
fast four
runs cracking boundary  Mitesh
Chauhan Absolute Fantastic Pushpa will
not bow down and will not stop
5359 N
Las has been sent this time and
back to back cut boundaries in the mid-wicket area
4 of 17 from Pho
Mitesh N Dazzlers 63
Faw clean
bowled excellent bowling
finally Parash Ram
got success and very well played by
Mitesh 40 of 18 ball Sen Phos
hit across the seven seas seven fours
strike raid off
22.22 5.5 63 P22
So The over will end with two runs
After six overs two A on Dazzlers Now
how many runs will Gautam and Siddhesh make in the coming two overs
Six over 65 P22 N Dazzlers
and the ball went very high Cameraman
caught it
Absolute Fantastic it flew like a
rocket into the clouds into the galaxy
six
runs He has broken the earth and above that too
Cameraman
T
lock Sish
this heart wants a turn  Siddhesh
More hit a four 6.2 76 runs 26 16
balls one four and two sixes
oh very lucky Siddhesh More took the luck
tablet white ball keeper misses backward region
the fielder misses
so three extras 6.2 79
Fatu Siddhesh More interested in only
delivering but hitting not for a single he
will cover all the runs in maximum hitting
6.3 79
Fatu comes back for two
runs 16 runs so far in four balls board
6.4 81 Fatu last two balls coming up off the
save
over bar only single
run
at 6.52 two wickets for n Dazzlers
now last ball of the save over coming
up Gautam on
strike plain bowled goal batsman got
clean bowled
after seven overs 82 p in n Dazzlers took
sen gun 82 pth Praneeth Parab and Siddhesh
More both are on fire these both Pushpa on
fire seven overs 82  Pati now the last over in this first
innings semi-final
one only
single so second semi-final coming up MI
BL vs
Howden
captain ready for the
toss MI BL vs Howden the semi-final
to MI BL captain howden captain is ready
for the toss we are
waiting for the Howden
captain it's very good field
Udi Mar fielding
performance by Prateek De 7.34 A Diesels
last three balls first
innings it's been given wide outside off the
line 853 N Diesels
taken very well catch taken by
Ramesh so very well played Sish More 30 off 21
balls and
looking to clear the long run of the region and long run
of the match
7 at 85 four Kisiki hogi jeet aur kisiki hogi har
N
Diesels
going for two runs towards the swell
and it's our run out very
good throw
so Prateek took a good throw from sle
region 7.5f
now the last ball of the first innings
ICICI Lord Brokers Premier League
semi-final
One N Dejlo vs Pink Panthers
Final Ball
Now Swinging
Ball's out Stumping out So a gun 86 C
Pink Panthers
need 87 runs to win Fan to enter So 87
target for Pink Panthers to
chase So take short break and come back
Semi-final First is on In
the game of life Stay protected with
ICICI Lord Health Insurance Junk
Food Colour Choice
Energy
Low In the game of life Stay protected with
ICICI Lord Health Insurance Power
Risto
[Music]
In the game of life Stay protected with
ICICI Lord Health Insurance
[Music]
Jump Food Colour
Choice Energy
Low In the game of life Stay protected with
ICICI Lord Health Insurance Power
Risto
[Music]
Dhar
Gaya to One Make Some Nose Jordaar Talia Semi-
final One Second innings will start The
target is 87 to chase
First ball Very good shot Boundary line ke bahar
Yeh gayi for four
First ball
strike
Vishram First ball for Pratik Kadam Non
strike and Ankur Jan started The
proceedings already started with from
N  Dazzlers
fielder goes deep for four runs on the first ball at cover he turns right
there
fielder turns right four runs and the fielder is on the other side he turns a
bit
two balls eight runs due to due factor the
fielder turns right there back to back
four consecutive
boundaries just leg stump outside leg stump for
white
ball two balls nine runs good start Pink
Panthers
Vishram has made the opposition team
cautious this
time in the gap there
Messi and Ronaldo were trying to
stop him with their football
skills but it went out
in the gap three balls 13 runs Pink Panthers got a start
firing start target is 87 to
chase this time trying to hit big shots over the stumps after four just
ball 1 for no loss at
Brokes Premier League semi-final one in
progress 87 target given by a to p
pant cheeky
cut by feed down at shut third
man for b bone p path last ball coming up off
first over
current t 16 record just
10  Taken catch fantastic at long on Ankur
Jan sen number jersey thala for
region done the magic
looking for the big one and
gone so good come back by Ankur Jan the bowler 14
runs conceded but you got the important
wicket wicket Prati Kadam caught Rajit bowled
Ankur first ball Prati Kadam caught
so Vishram still in
one over 14 for one and 14 for one Pink Pink
Panthers
Siddhesh More all-rounder batted well in the
first innings 30 off 21 and
26 now with the ball is so
one more power play only to feed out
side circle is allowed one fielder deep
extra
cover a one to was long on
good fielding good little single
run.  72 Na Fam Coming
6.5 New man
Ramesh Suresh comes into batting
Ramesh very good
bowling takes the advantage of being hide bowler,
read the button completely and put pressure
maintain line
length.  Four Pink Panthers
good stop late outside edge shot to third man
region
1.31 for one Pink
Panthers score is in
danger now the score is
17 70 runs needed 6.3 overs left 70
runs 39
balls Had he shot a wicket at the non-striker's end, he could have got a few wickets but he is
not taking any risk if he loses one run
1.41 for one Pink Panthers
69 to get from coming in 38
balls Siddhesh More very good bowling four
balls four
runs absolute good bowling
the first one and 14 runs now this way good come back
from n Dazzlers
five balls five
singles 1.5 at 19
one swing and miss down the track looking to play
for the big one
and they did not get the connection seems they have
not matched up Bumble Pete Gun 19 Four Pink
Panthers
after two 19 for one Pink Panthers 68 runs coming in
36 balls to centre of the pop maximum can be done
Inside circle four fielder should be inside circle
mandatory non power
play Praneeth Parab comes on strike at pole position Vishram
plays it lightly towards point
steals a run
2 p 67 to get from coming 5.5 35 Ball
67 runs required at around
11.50 Plays yards for a single Runs
two doubles two on 21 66 runs and 34 balls left
and the fielder fails to catch it The
ball goes outside the boundary for four Top
edged and taken for four at backward
region Two dati 25 62 runs 33 balls current
run 10 and required at 11.27 Another
good
shot six runs into the comment box bottom
excellent sixer from
Vishram 27 11 balls four fours and a
maximum
Hits two dc 31 fw pips
Wanted to cut The ball bounced a little and went
into the hands of the keeper 2.5 31
One good this time  Bowling wide ball point
by 2.5 32 fw 55 fm 31
ts reverse hit st fed at short third man he will take
strike single to end one over no game over
33 Pink
Panthers 54 Required from five overs
left after three overs 33
fw b one
wicket 54 in five overs
Rahul Panchal comes to bowling
chha 3 one
wicket catch it catch it and he
took a good catch at kor regen
catches finish
match Rahul Panchal first ball ma dhamaka
karela
chha catch taken by Gautam he is not
Gambhir 3.1 33
fw new batsman coming at number four
Hemant still in this match N
Diesels and Pink Panthers and this big wicket
28 14 balls four fours one six excellent
batting performance once strongly Tall
Vishram Sak very well played
a batting par Hemant Ambekar
Naveen Palandaj
three 3.13
outside edge taken single at third man sh thd  Man
fielder 3.2 34 ft 53 runs no
20 balls left
so now current end required almost 7
10.20
11.36 Just one acceleration of one run to get
the current end required
same run this time I
go two steps back he can take a catch but
reflection is very much
required he try to take two but was over
him for
run 3.38 Pink Panthers 49 to get and coming
balls good shot by
Ramesh played in the field
at long off
two runs taken 4 ft 3.4
47 runs to get from 26
now his shot once again lucky the batsman
is good stop at long off
region only single run this time 3.5 41
two very close encounter close chance
swing and miss to end of the
over sot 41  F Four over left 46 to get
ICICI Lombard Brokers Premier League
Season Two Day Two Even Sporting Partner
Brand Next
Media It's a great first day and also Now
the second day Super exciting Super Sunday Funday
Now we are at the semi-final round The
first semi-final progress
back to back Praneet Parab doing something
magical bowling
Now 46 from 3.4
Now Very good catch excellent taken Shusher running catch
from was long off and very good catch
taken there So wicket
number
three Ramesh Departs
10 of 10 Bal no 4
dti 41
Fth completely here in this match both
teams and 50 equation chances of win Let's see Now
One quality over and one big
over n Dazzlers
Let's see Pink Panthers can make something
special Now the new
batsman Pratesh Pawar on strike
To what outside chance for the keeper to take the
batsman survive
45 from 20
Now Excellent bowling from Praneet Parab  Pradip
Eswar's last ball, Praneet,
and what's left here, the dream is shattered.
43 runs after five overs.
Need 44 runs in the next three overs
and this seamer is outside off for four.
5.2 47 4th Now 40 runs
[applause]
[music]
Balls 40 runs 16
balls swing a
miss good bowling here N Dazzlers has
kept a good grip and bowled well.
15 runs
40 15 balls 40 runs
47 4th Now 40 from 14 balls
40 from 14
balls the passing marks of 40
14 once again Rahul
Panchal very good
bowling 40 runs now 13 balls a big hit will do
something amazing and will achieve something Hemant
and Pritesh and
then went into the commentary box very
good fielding by me on the boundary line for four.
So six on the gun 51 4th over left 36 to
get shot long off for four
ICC Lord Prakas Premier
League Season Two Day
Two Sporting Partner Next
Media 10 Good bowling Siddhesh More now
into the at stumps
misses 36 now from 11 balls
only a single
run so 35 from 10
balls 3.5 every ball once again
swing and
miss Siddhesh More turning the
course of the
match Three
balls only a single
run in this so far 35 not from 11 balls only a single run so 35 from 10 balls 3.5 every ball once
again swing and
miss Green bowls letham bails go good bye Tata bye
6.5 52 f f Siddhesh More on
strike 6.5 52 on
four and 35 runs now needed in seven balls
so a couple of runs and that will be the end of the
over Number seven
hits 54 f f and they require 33 to get in the
final
over Still the discussion is on who will be the man
of the match Mite Chauhan has played well 40 of
18 Siddesh More 21 with
16 by Siddhesh More took one  More wickets wickets
also so
coming up the final over
of the semi final one n dazzlers
will enter into the finals
single looking for to past
cover and they will go for one more
run going back for
run and
gun so three runs taken from amay so
now n dazzlers will be the first contender
to enter into the final
30 runs needed in five balls and this dot ball isi ke
saath n
dazzlers final me karenge enter aur unko hum
puchhenge final match or perform what happening
swing a
miss
7.37 par
five 30 from three so now just
time to celebrate the first
finalist here we go
last ball 28 r
required swing miss n dazzler entering
into the final one by 27 runs many much
congratulations ic i load brokers
premier league the first
finalist going path no it's
n dazzlers
error from my side rectified n dazzlers
so a dazzler very much congratulations
and will be calling the man of the
match  N Dazzlers
this is
Baazigar come quickly match Siddhesh More is back again
present
ok
everyone let Siddhesh More go ahead come
Siddhesh More
ji very well
played so make some noise for Siddhesh
turn 30 of 21 o and s and with the bowling